{
    "id": "50c79909271c4e7ba94f51ac193648bb",
    "title": "General English Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She is intelligent …………………… . she lacks experience.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "however",
                "even as",
                "even though"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They live ………………………. miles from here.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "plenty of",
                "lots of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "His rude remarks made her ………………… ..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cry",
                "to cry",
                "crying"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t speak English well, but I can make myself …………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "understand",
                "understood",
                "understanding"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My mother makes wine …………………… .. blackberries.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "out of",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Could you ……………………… the kids while I go shopping?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "look for",
                "look at",
                "look after"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He never drives fast because he is afraid ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to crash",
                "of crashing",
                "with crashing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I’m …………………….. working abroad. Could you help me?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "interested to",
                "interested in",
                "interested at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They often go hiking ………………… . going to school.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "without",
                "instead of",
                "instead"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I spent the whole day in bed ……………………… to work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "instead of to go",
                "instead of going",
                "instead to go"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}